(Penny:)Okay.
(Leonard:)Her apartment's on the fourth floor,
elevator is broken, you're gonna...
Oh, you're just gonna be done?
Okay, cool, thanks.
(Leonard:)- I guess we'll just bring it up ourselves.
- I hardly think so.
(Leonard:)Why not?
(Sheldon:)Well, we don't have a dolly...
(Sheldon:)...or lifting belts,
or any measurable upper-body strength.
(Leonard:)We don't need strength.
We're physicists.
(Leonard:)We are the intellectual
descendents of Archimedes.
(Leonard:)Give me a fulcrum and a lever
and I can move the Earth.
It's just a matter... I don't have this!
I do not have this!
(Sheldon:)Archimedes would be so proud.
(Leonard:)Do you have any ideas?
(Sheldon:)Yes, but they all involve
a Green Lantern and a power ring.
(Leonard:)Easy. Easy.
Okay. Now we've got an inclined plane.
(Leonard:)Force required to lift is reduced
by the sine of the angle of the stairs...